howtolearn.com 2019-12-03

# Privacy Policy | How to Learn

Thank you for visiting our HowtoLearn.com website. Because your privacy is important to us. we provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected or utilized when you use this site.

This page contains the privacy policy for HowtoLearn.com and all its related websites.

 **What Information Do We Collect?  
**

In order to personalize your experience, (your information helps us better understand your individual needs, we collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, place an order or fill out a form. Your continued use of the website indicates you agree with this data collection and you may choose whether or not to use this website if you do not wish to have any of this information collected. When registering or filling out any of the above on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, occupation, mailing address, phone number or credit card information, as well as which other educational subjects you may be interested in. Legally, if you place an order on the site, you will input your personal information in order to place the order. Your Credit card information is provided to one of two third party secure processing sites, depending on your choice. These two sites are 1shoppingcart.com and Paypal. (Each of them has a separate privacy policy about how they safeguard your information and you may read that on their sites.) You may, however, choose to visit our site anonymously. Like most websites we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. We do have Google advertisements on this website and they collect data via their privacy policy. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them. The data controller is The Center for New Discoveries in Learning, Inc. and you may contact the business directly at 6375 South Pecos Rd., Suite 216, Las Vegas, NV 89120, or you may call 702 329-6302 if you require more information.

 **What do we use your information for?**

  * In order to personalize your experience, any of the information we collect about you may be used in one or more of the following ways:
  * To improve our website because we continuously strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and questions. We may share or sell your name and email information with third parties for marketing or other purposes without your consent. To administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other site feature and to send you periodic emails.
  * The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. You may unsubscribe from emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.

 **How do we protect your information?  
**We implement a wide variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access the website. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is encrypted to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. We use a third party secured website to facilitate any credit card transactions and they follow all legal guidelines to keep your credit card information secure.

 **Do we use cookies?  
**Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
**

Unless this website is sold to another party or business, or we are using a trusted third party to assist us in operating our website, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information such as your email address. Again, we do have trusted third parties, such as our email provider, Aweber, shopping cart (1shoppingcart.com and paypal) and various affiliate partners, each of whom has their own privacy policies, who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, and each of those parties has separately agreed to safeguard and keep this information confidential in their privacy policies. We may however, release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses and should our website be sold to another person or entity, they may be entitled to secure your name and email address or other information you have filled out on various forms on the site. For example, Personal information, such as your email address will be used to make automated decisions to contact you if you have requested to subscribe to our newsletter, placed an order on the site, contacted us via the contact form on our website, or emailed us directly. In order to communicate with you, we may also share your email address with various shippers such as the USPS, Fed Ex, UPS or other, so that you may track your shipment. Additionally, we use Google ads on the site, and they may use their cookies to show you more relevant ads based on your interest, or to help improve search capabilities on this website. Providing any personal information is not mandatory, and it is at your discretion to provide any information at all. We are doing our very best to ensure that this policy is fully transparent, written in simple English and should you have any questions at all, you may contact us via our contact form, telephone number, email address or write us a letter. If something is accidentally not covered in this Privacy Policy and you would like to see it covered, just let us know and we are happy to add more information to it.

 **Third party links  
**We include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy polices. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback you may send us about these sites. They include Google, other search engines who index our site, and private advertisers, again, all of whom have their own privacy policies for which can assume no liability should you choose to click through and view those sites.

 **Online privacy policy only  
**This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms and Conditions  
**Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the website.

 **Your Consent  
**By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy

 **Changes to our privacy policy  
**Changes to this privacy policy will be made available on this webpage only and when updated, we may email you as well if you have provided your email address as a newsletter subscriber.

If you wish to contact us, you may do so by using our Contact button or any other of our contact information on the site and it is also provided above.
